[
  {
    "questionNumber": 1,
    "question": "Which type of investment offer bigger capital and income growth?",
    "options": {
      "A": "investment with little risk",
      "B": "investment with high risk",
      "C": "investment with moderate risk",
      "D": "investment with no risk"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 2,
    "question": "Share price are generally higher in the following situations:\nI. when there are more buyers than shares available for sale\nII. when the company is making a good profit\nIII. when the country economy is unstable\nIV. when the interest rates are higher",
    "options": {
      "A": "I and III",
      "B": "II and IV",
      "C": "I and II",
      "D": "III and IV"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 3,
    "question": "The factors that do NOT influence the choice of deposits in a bank include:\nI. prevailing market condition\nII. the gender of the depositor\nIII. the funds available for investment\nIV. the academic qualification of the depositor",
    "options": {
      "A": "I and II",
      "B": "I and III",
      "C": "II and III",
      "D": "II and IV"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 4,
    "question": "What does the term “Prospect” refer to?",
    "options": {
      "A": "percentage of closing deal",
      "B": "potential customer",
      "C": "potential product",
      "D": "the future of the agent"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 5,
    "question": "The following are secondary objectives of investment EXCEPT:",
    "options": {
      "A": "safety",
      "B": "hedging inflation",
      "C": "retirement income",
      "D": "achieving financial freedom"
    },
    "answer": "A"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 6,
    "question": "Which of the following is considered INCONSISTENT with after-sales service?",
    "options": {
      "A": "Providing a basis for future sales on current needs",
      "B": "Explaining the policy’s provisions, terms and conditions",
      "C": "Establishing the customer/agent relationship",
      "D": "Strengthening the customer/agent relationship"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 7,
    "question": "With regard to the investment-linked life policy, the uncertainty of investment gains or losses is shifted to:",
    "options": {
      "A": "Insurers",
      "B": "Insured",
      "C": "Agents",
      "D": "Brokers"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 8,
    "question": "Using the dual policy method, calculate the cash value of 5000 units purchased at an offer price of RM3 and sold at a bid price of RM1 with a mortality charge of 1% and RM100 policy fee.",
    "options": {
      "A": "RM 14,750",
      "B": "RM 4,850",
      "C": "RM 4,600",
      "D": "RM 9,350"
    },
    "answer": "B"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 9,
    "question": "What are the benefits of investing in investment-linked funds?\nI. Diversification\nII. Flexibility\nIII. Expertise\nIV. Easy access to well diversified investments",
    "options": {
      "A": "I, II and III",
      "B": "II, III and IV",
      "C": "I, III and IV",
      "D": "I, II, III and IV"
    },
    "answer": "D"
  },
  {
    "questionNumber": 10,
    "question": "Investment-linked life insurance policies must have a minimum death benefit of:",
    "options": {
      "A": "RM 3,000",
      "B": "RM 4,000",
      "C": "RM 5,000",
      "D": "RM 6,000"
    },
    "answer": "C"
  }
]
